Martha Graham Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music Inventory (Box 1-118; 122; 124-197)
  - Choreographed Works (Box 1-191, 193-194)
    - Serenata Morisca (1916) Composer: Enrico Tarenghi, Enrico Tarenghi’s title: Serenata, op. 13.; Choreographed by Ted Shawn and performed by Martha Graham on Denishawn tours (1921-1923) and in the Greenwich Village Follies (1923-1925).
      - Photocopy full score, orchestrated by J. McPhee (Box-folder 176/1)
      - Copyist transparency parts (Box-folder 176/2)
      - Set of parts (Box-folder 176/3)
      - Photocopy extra parts (Box-folder 176/4)
    - Serpent Heart see Cave of the Heart
    - Seter, Mordecai see Legend of Judith; Part Real-Part Dream; Point of Crossing
    - Six Pieces, op. 6 see Episodes: Part I
    - Starer, Robert see Holy Jungle; Lady of the House of Sleep; Phaedra; Visionary Recital; Secular Games
    - Steps in the Street (1989) Composer: Wallingford Reigger, Reigger’s title: New Dance.; Reconstructed in 1989; originally part of Chronicle (1936).
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 177/1)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 177/2-5)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 177/6-10)
      - Steps in the Street, orchestrated by Justin Dello Joio (reduced) (Box-folder 178/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 178/2-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 178/5-7)
      - Transparency master (Box-folder 178/8)
    - Stravinsky, Igor see Rite of Spring
    - Stroman, Susan see But Not for Me
    - Surinach, Carlos see Acrobats of God; Embattled Garden; Owl and the Pussycat
    - Táncszviť[Dance Suite] see Temptations of the Moon
    - Tangled Night (1986) Composer: Klaus Egge, Egge’s title: Piano Concerto no. 2, op. 21.
      - Published full scores (2) (Box-folder 179/1)
      - Published parts (Box-folder 179/2)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 179/3)
    - Temptations of the Moon (1986) Composer: Béla Bartók, Bartók’s title: Táncszviť [Dance Suite].
      - Published full score (Box-folder 180/1)
      - Photocopy published full score (Box-folder 180/2)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 180/3-5)
      - Ozalid published parts (Box-folder 181/1)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 181/2-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 182/1-6)
    - Time of Snow, A (1968) Composer: Norman Dello Joio, Dello Joio’s title: Heloïse and Abelard.
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 183/1)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 183/2)
      - Photocopy full score (Box-folder 183/3)
      - Photocopy piano/vocal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 183/4)
      - Photocopy piano/vocal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 183/5)
      - Photocopy piano/vocal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 183/6)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 184/1-2)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 184/3)
    - Toch, Ernst see Harlequinade
    - Transitions (1934) Composer: Lehman Engle
      - Trumpet part in ink (Box-folder 194/12)
    - Triumph of St. Joan Symphony, The see Triumph of St. Joan
    - Triumph of St. Joan, The (1951) Composer: Norman Dello Joio, Rechoreographed as Seraphic Dialogue (1955).; Dello Joio’s title: The Triumph of St. Joan Symphony (version of opera, The Triumph of St. Joan).
      - Ozalid full score, arranged for chamber orchestra by Abraham Skulsky (Box-folder 171/1)
      - Ozalid full score, arranged for chamber orchestra by Abraham Skulsky (Box-folder 171/2)
      - Ink piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 171/3)
      - Ozalid parts (old set) (Box-folder 171/4-6)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 173/1-4)
      - Copyist’s transparencies, parts (Box-folder 174/1)
      - Ozalid string parts (new set) (Box-folder 174/2)
      - Ozalid parts, extra parts (Box-folder 174/3-5)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 175/1-5)
      - Sing parts (Box-folder 172)
    - Trois Gnossiennes (1926) Composer: Erik Satie
      - Piano score for no. 2; photocopy laid in ink (Box-folder 194/13)
    - Varèse, Edgar see Ecuatorial; Judith
    - Ved en Ung kunstners baare [At the Bier of a Young Artist] see Acts of Light
    - Visionary Recital (1961) Composer: Robert Starer
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 185/1)
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 185/2)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 185/3)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, no choreographic notes (Box-folder 185/4)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 186/1-3)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 186/4-5)
    - Voyage (1953) Composer: William Schuman
      - Ozalid full score (Box-folder 187/1)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 187/2)
      - Published piano score, with choreographic notes (Box-folder 187/3)
      - Piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (incomplete) (Box-folder 187/4)
      - Ozalid parts, woodwinds (Box-folder 188/1)
      - Ozalid parts, horn, piano (Box-folder 188/2)
      - Ozalid parts, string (Box-folder 188/3)
      - Ozalid extra parts (Box-folder 188/4)
    - Webern, Anton see Episodes, Part I
    - Weisshaus, Imre see Satyric Festival Song
    - Wilderness Stair see Diversion of Angels
    - Witch of Endor (1965) Composer: William Schuman
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (vol 1) (Box-folder 189/1)
      - Ozalid piano rehearsal score, with choreographic notes (vol 1) (Box-folder 189/2)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 189/3-4)
      - Ozalid parts (Box-folder 190/1-4)
      - Extra parts (Box-folder 191/1-3)
    - Zamfir, [Geheorghe] see Flute of Pan
  - Supplementary Music (Box 192-193, 195-197)
    - Music by Louis Horst, composed and/or arranged for the Martha Graham Dance technique classes, circa 1927-1929 (Box-folder 192/1)
    - Photocopy of above (Box-folder 192/2)
    - Twenty-three pieces by Clifford Bowens, with audiocassette (Box-folder 192/4)
    - Elite Sync by Adam Ben-David, (audiocassette) (Box-folder 192/5)
    - Sonata for Two Violins by Mordecai Seter, (2 scores) (Box-folder 195/1)
    - Ricercar by Mordecai Seter, (score) (Box-folder 195/2)
    - Chacone et Scherzo pour Piano by Mordecai Seter, (score) (Box-folder 195/3)
    - Yemenite Suite by Mordecai Seter, (score) (Box-folder 195/4)
    - Movement for Piano by Yeshiva Lakner, (score) (Box-folder 195/5)
    - Sextett by Yeshiva Lakner, (score and parts: Fl, Ob, Cl in C, Cor in C, Fag, Piano) (Box-folder 195/6)
    - String Quartet by Josef Tal, (Score and Parts: Violin I, Violin II, Viola, Cello) (Box-folder 195/7)
    - Dance (duet for two flutes) by Josef Tal, (score) (Box-folder 195/8)
    - Out of the Dust by Ben-Zion Orgad, (score) (Box-folder 195/9)
    - Morning Stars for alto, flute, violin, viola, and cello by Ben-Zion Orgad, (score) (Box-folder 195/10)
    - Celestial Spheres for alto, flute, violin, viola, and cello by Ben-Zion Orgad, (score) (Box-folder 195/11)
    - Songs of Rahel by Abraham Daus (two violas and flute) (Box-folder 195/12)
    - Chronique by Carlos Surinach, (Ozalid full score) (Box-folder 193/9)
    - Chronique by Carlos Surinach, (piano score) (Box-folder 193/10)
    - Two scenes from Anthony and Cleopatra by Samuel Barber, (published full score) (Box-folder 193/16)
    - Lord Hear my Longing by Johann Sebastian Bach; orchestrated by Walton (Box-folder 196/1)
    - Concerto for Derabucca and Strings by Halim El-Dabh, (ozalid full score) (Box-folder 196/2)
    - Music for Mouths, Marimba, Nbira, and Roto-toms by Malcolm Forsyth, (published full score) (Box-folder 196/3)
    - Tomorrow the Festivals, op. 130 by Alan Hovaness, (ozalid full score) (Box-folder 196/4)
    - Sonata for Horn, Trumpet, and Trombone by François Poulanc, (published score and parts) (Box-folder 196/5)
    - Notturno (Jacob’s Dream), op. 44 by Karol Rathaus, (published full score) (Box-folder 196/6)
    - Night Music by George Rochberg, (published full score) (Box-folder 196/7)
    - String Quartet by George Rochberg, (published score and parts) (Box-folder 196/8)
    - Dance Sonata, op. 24 by Marion Bauer, (photocopy piano score) (Box-folder 197/1)
    - Prelude by Paul Creston, (pencil score/ink score) (Box-folder 197/2)
    - Myriologue, A by David Diamond, (holograph in ink piano score) (Box-folder 197/3)
    - Songs of an Ancient People, op. 10 by Lehman Engle, (piano sketch in ink; ozalid piano score) (Box-folder 197/4)
    - Dance by Herbert Haufreucht, (ozalid piano score) (Box-folder 197/5)
    - To Martha Graham by Charles Naginski, (ozalid piano score) (Box-folder 197/6)
    - Dance by Paul Nordoff, (ink piano score) (Box-folder 197/7)
    - Evocation by Wallingford Riegger, (ink piano score, four-hands) (Box-folder 197/8)
    - Eclogue by Dane Rudman, (photostat piano score) (Box-folder 197/9)
    - Dance by Elie Siegmeister, (ink piano score) (Box-folder 197/10)
    - Six pieces for solo voice by Imre Weisshause, (vocal score) (Box-folder 197/11)
    - Four Songs by Pelkam Whyte, (ozalid piano-vocal score) (Box-folder 197/12)
    - The Train to Johannisberg (composer unknown), (ozalid piano-vocal score) (Box-folder 197/13)
    - G by Carlos Chávez, (piano score) (Box-folder 197/14)
    - Tarantella in E minor by W. Lomas, (piano score) (Box-folder 197/14)
    - Tarentella, op. 26 by Théodore Lack, (piano score) (Box-folder 197/14)
    - Toccata, op. 1 by Serge Prokofiev, (piano score) (Box-folder 197/14)
    - 3rd Gymnopédie by Erik Satie, (piano score) (Box-folder 197/14)
    - Dance by Gustave Ferrari, (piano score) (Box-folder 197/14)
    - Music from Louis Horst’s Dance classes (Box-folder 197/15)
    - “Star Spangled Banner”, (published orchestration) (Box-folder 197/16)
    - Dance Symphony by Aaron Copland, (photocopy 2nd flute part) (Box-folder 197/17)
    - Fragments (Box-folder 197/18)
- Scrapbooks (Box 308-376)
  The Martha Graham Collection contains an especially rich collection of Scrapbooks that span from 1926 to 1976. Documents contained within the scrapbooks include the official invitation from Germany to participate in the 1936 Olympics and Graham’s carbon copy of her refusal; transcripts of a German radio program from 1941; telegrams and notes of congratulations from luminaries such as Helen Hayes, Mary Wigman, Lincoln Kirstein, Sir Frederick Ashton, Svetlana Beriosova, and Michael Somes; and significant information on the Graham Company’s European tours during the Cold War. Other materials contained within the scrapbooks include invitations, speeches, fan mail, interviews, photographs, correspondence, reviews, and letters of tribute. For similar materials, the reader should see other parts of the collection, including Clippings; Programs; Writings By and About Martha Graham; and New York City Season and National and International Touring.
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - 1926-1929 (Box 308)
  - 1929-1930 (Box 309)
  - 1932-1933 (Box 310)
  - 1935-1936 (Box 311)
  - 1936 Tour (Box 312)
  - 1936-1937 (Box 313)
  - 1938-1939 (Box 314)
  - 1939 Tour (Box 315)
  - 1939-1940 (Box 316)
  - 1940 Tour (Box 317)
  - 1940-1941 (Box 318)
  - 1941-1942 (Box 319)
  - 1941-1950 (Box 320 A, B)
  - 1942-1944 (Box 321)
  - 1944-1945 (Box 322)
  - 1945-1946 (Box 323)
  - 1946 Tour (Box 324)
  - 1946-1947 (Box 325)
  - 1949-1951 (Box 326)
  - 1950 (Box 327)
  - 1950 Tour (Box 328)
  - 1950-1967 (Box 329)
  - 1955 Tour (Asia) (Box 330)
  - 1955 Tour (Singapore) (Box 331)
  - 1955 Tour (Indonesia, Burma) (Box 332)
  - 1955 Tour (Japan), 2 volumes (Box 333)
  - 1955 Tour (India, Pakistan) (Box 334)
  - 1955 Tour (Philippines) (Box 335)
  - 1955 Tour (Japan) and 1955 NYC Season, 2 volumes (Box 336)
  - 1955-1956 Tour (Israel, Greece) (Box 337)
  - 1956 Tour (India, Pakistan, Iran, Ceylon), 2 volumes (Box 338)
  - 1957-1963 (Box 339)
  - 1957 Tour (Berlin) (Box 340)
  - 1958 (Box 341)
  - 1958 Tour (Israel) (Box 342)
  - 1958 (Box 343)
  - 1958 NYC Season (Box 344)
  - 1959 NYC Season (Box 345)
  - 1960 NYC Season (Box 346)
  - 1960 Capezio Award; 1961 General (Box 347)
  - 1961 NYC Season (Box 348)
  - 1962 Tour (Israel) (Box 349)
  - 1962 Tour (Turkey, Yugoslavia) (Box 350)
  - 1962 (Box 351)
  - 1962 Tour (Poland, Germany, Sweden) (Box 352)
  - 1962 NYC Season (Box 353)
  - 1962 Tour (Finland, Netherlands, Germany) (Box 354)
  - 1963 (September-October "Congressional Issue"); 1963 (October Eskin Court Case) (Box 355)
  - 1963 NYC Season (Box 356)
  - 1963 Tour (Edinburgh Festival and London) (Box 357)
  - 1963 (Box 358)
  - 1964 (Box 359)
  - 1965 (Box 360)
  - 1965 (Box 361)
  - 1966 (Box 362)
  - 1966 (Box 363)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 364)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 365)
  - 1968 (Box 366)
  - 1968-1969, 2 volumes (Box 367)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 368)
  - 1970 Tour (U.S.) (Box 369)
  - 1970 (Box 370)
  - 1970 (Box 371)
  - 1973-1975 (Box 372)
  - 1974 Tour (Asia) (Box 373)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 374)
  - 1976 (Box 375)
  - 1941-1951 Martha Graham Dance School and Martha Graham School of Contemporary Dance (Box 376)
- Photographic Material (Box 239-273)
  The Photographic Material series consists of over 8,000 photographs, dating from Graham’s Denishawn days through the late 1980s. In addition, there are family photographs and a number of informal shots taken at fund-raising events by former Graham board chair, Arnold Weissberger.
  Primarily arranged alphabetically by name of choreographic work.
  - Acrobats of God
    - Hinkson, McGehee, MG, Powell, other (Box-folder 239/1)
    - Hinkson, McGehee, MG, Wood, others (Box-folder 239/2)
    - Kanda, McGehee, MG, Winter, Wood, others (Box-folder 239/3)
    - Kanda, MG, Wood (Box-folder 239/4)
    - Kanda, Taylor (Box-folder 239/5)
    - McGehee, MG, Wood (Box-folder 239/6)
    - McGehee, MG, Wood (incl. negatives) (Box-folder 258/2)
    - McGehee, Ross (Box-folder 239/7, 258/4)
    - McGehee, Wood (Box-folder 239/8)
    - McGehee, MG, Winter (Box-folder 258/1)
    - McGehee, MG, Winter (negatives) (Box-folder 258/3)
    - MG (Box-folder 239/9)
    - MG (incl. negatives) (Box-folder 258/5)
    - MG, Powell (Box-folder 239/10)
    - MG, Powell, Wood (Box-folder 239/11)
    - MG, Ross, Winter (Box-folder 239/12, 258/6)
    - MG, Ross, Winter, Wood (Box-folder 239/13, 258/7)
    - MG, Winter, Wood, [Yuriko], other (Box-folder 258/8)
    - MG, Wood (Box-folder 239/14, 258/9)
    - MG, Wood, other (Box-folder 258/10)
    - MG, Wood, Yuriko (Box-folder 239/15)
    - Wood (Box-folder 239/16)
    - Group (negative) (Box-folder 258/11)
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 239/17)
    - Rehearsals for film (Box-folder 239/18)
    - Proofs (Box-folder 239/19)
  - Acts of Light
    - Asakawa, Walker (Box-folder 239/20, 258/12)
    - Dakin (Box-folder 239/21)
    - Garay, White (Box-folder 239/22)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 239/23)
    - Lyman, Sparling (Box-folder 239/24)
    - Lyman, Wengerd, group (Box-folder 239/25)
    - Sparling (Box-folder 239/26)
  - Adorations
    - Asakawa, Walker (Box-folder 239/27)
    - Delamo, Eilber, Homsey, Lyman, Maloney, Sparling, Walker Delamo, Eilber, Homsey, Maloney (Box-folder 239/28)
    - Eilber, Lyman, McGuire (Box-folder 239/29)
    - Gray, Maloney, Wengerd, Yu (Box-folder 239/30)
    - Homsey, Maloney (Box-folder 239/31)
    - Homsey, Maloney, other (Box-folder 239/32)
    - Maloney, McGuire (Box-folder 239/33)
  - Alcestis
    - Hodes (Linda), McGehee, MG, Winter, others (Box-folder 239/34)
    - Kuch, Winter, others (Box-folder 258/13)
    - MG (Box-folder 239/35)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 239/36)
    - MG, Ross (incl. negative) (Box-folder 258/14)
    - MG, Ross, Taylor (Box-folder 239/37)
    - MG, Ross, Taylor, group (Box-folder 239/38)
    - MG, Taylor (Box-folder 239/39)
    - MG, group (Box-folder 239/40)
    - MG, others (Box-folder 239/41, 258/15)
    - MG, women (negative) (Box-folder 239/42)
    - Taylor (Box-folder 239/43)
    - Taylor, MG, Wood, others (Box-folder 239/44)
    - Taylor, others (Box-folder 239/45)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 239/46)
    - Group (Box-folder 239/47)
    - Set (Box-folder 239/48)
  - American Document
    - Hawkins (Box-folder 239/49)
    - Hawkins, Maslow, women (Box-folder 239/50)
    - Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 258/16)
    - MG (Box-folder 239/51)
  - Andromache’s Lament
    - Brown, Ruddy (Box-folder 239/52)
    - Foreman, Morin, Ruddy (Box-folder 239/53)
    - Lyman (Box-folder 239/44)
    - Ruddy (Box-folder 239/55)
  - Appalachian Spring
    - Asakawa, Gutelius, Lapsezon, other (Box-folder 240/1, 258/17)
    - Asakawa, Gutelius, Lapsezon, Wood (Marne), other (Box-folder 258/18)
    - Capucilli, Littleford (Box-folder 240/2)
    - Carter (Box-folder 258/18)
    - Carter, other (Box-folder 258/21)
    - Carter, Gutelius (Box-folder 240/3, 258/19)
    - Carter, Gutelius, Walker, others (Box-folder 258/20)
    - Cohan, Turney, Winter (Box-folder 240/4, 258/22)
    - Cohan, Turney, Winter, others (Box-folder 240/5, 258/22)
    - Cohan, Winter, others (Box-folder 240/6, 258/23)
    - Cole, Hinkson, McGehee, Yuriko (Box-folder 240/7)
    - Cole, Hinkson, others (Box-folder 240/8)
    - Cole, Hodes, McGehee, MG, Ross, Turney, Winter, Yuriko (Box-folder 258/24)
    - Cole, Hodes, MG, Ross, Turney, Winter, Yuriko (Box-folder 258/25)
    - Eilber, others [Kimura, Wengerd] (Box-folder 240/9)
    - Fonaroff, Lang, Mazia, MG, O’Donnell, Yuriko (Box-folder 240/10)
    - Gray, Wengerd (Box-folder 240/11)
    - Gutelius (Box-folder 240/12)
    - Gutelius, Walker, others (Box-folder 240/13)
    - Hawkins, Cunningham, others (Box-folder 258/26)
    - Hawkins, Cunningham, MG, O’Donnell (Box-folder 265/1)
    - Hawkins, MG, O’Donnell, Lang, Yuriko, other (Box-folder 240/14)
    - Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 240/15)
    - Hawkins, MG, O’Donnell, others (Box-folder 240/16)
    - Hawkins, MG, other (Box-folder 240/17)
    - Hodes (Stuart) (Box-folder 240/18)
    - Hodes (Stuart), MG (Box-folder 240/19, 258/28)
    - Hodes, McGehee, MG, Ross, Turney, Winter, Yuriko (Box-folder 258/27)
    - Hodes (Stuart), MG, Ross, Turney (Box-folder 240/20)
    - Hodes, Turney (Box-folder 240/21)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 240/22)
    - Kimura, Sparling, Wengerd (Box-folder 240/23)
    - Kimura, Wengerd (Box-folder 240/24)
    - Kimura, [Wengerd], others (Box-folder 240/25)
    - Lang (Box-folder 240/26)
    - Littleford (Box-folder 240/27)
    - Lyman (Box-folder 240/28)
    - Lyman, Sparling, chorus (Box-folder 240/29)
    - MG (Box-folder 240/30)
    - MG (Box-folder 240/31)
    - MG (negative) (Box-folder 258/29)
    - MG, O’Donnell (Box-folder 240/32)
    - MG, Ross (Box-folder 240/33)
    - MG, others (Box-folder 240/34)
    - Nureyev, others [Eilber] (Box-folder 240/35)
    - O’Donnell (Box-folder 240/36)
    - Rooks (Box-folder 240/37)
    - Ross (Box-folder 240/38)
    - Sherman (Box-folder 240/40)
    - Sparling (Box-folder 240/41)
    - Walker (Box-folder 240/42)
    - Walker, others (Box-folder 240/43)
    - Wengerd (Box-folder 258/30)
    - White (Larry) (Box-folder 240/44)
    - Winter (Box-folder 240/45, 258/31)
    - Winter, others (Box-folder 258/32)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 258/33)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 240/46)
    - Contact sheets/proofs (Box-folder 240/47)
    - Slides (color) (Box-folder 258/34)
    - Slides (color) (Box-folder 258/35)
    - Group (Box-folder 240/48)
    - Scene drawings (Box-folder 240/49)
  - The Archaic House
    - Cohan, Louther, Ross, Thompson, others (Box-folder 241/1/)
    - Cohan, Powell, Ross, others (Box-folder 241/2)
    - Dakin, [Thompson], others (Box-folder 241/3)
    - Dakin, group (Box-folder 241/4)
  - Ardent Song
    - Cohan, Lang, Wood (Box-folder 241/5)
    - Hodes, McGehee, Taylor, Wood; Hodes, McGehee, Taylor, Wood,other (Box-folder 241/6)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 241/7)
    - Group (Box-folder 241/8)
  - Canticle for Innocent Comedians
    - Cohan, McGehee (Box-folder 241/9)
    - Cole, Hinkson, Hodes (Linda and Stuart) (Box-folder 241/10)
    - Cole, Hodes (Linda and Stuart) (Box-folder 241/11)
    - Hinkson (Box-folder 241/12)
    - Hinkson, and others (Box-folder 241/13)
    - Hodes (Linda and Stuart), Wood (Box-folder 241/14)
    - Hodes (Stuart) (Box-folder 241/15)
    - Lang, Ross (Box-folder 241/16)
    - Lapsezon (Box-folder 241/17)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 241/18, 259/1)
    - McGehee, Ross (Box-folder 241/19)
    - Ross (Box-folder 241/20)
    - Ross, Yuriko (Box-folder 241/21)
    - Winter (Box-folder 241/22)
    - Yuriko (Box-folder 241/23)
  - Cave of the Heart
    - Asakawa (Box-folder 241/24)
    - Asakawa, Hart, Parkes (Box-folder 241/25)
    - Brown, Capucilli (Box-folder 241/26)
    - Buglisi, White (Box-folder 241/27)
    - Cohan, McGehee (Box-folder 241/28)
    - Cohan, McGehee, Turney, Yuriko (Box-folder 241/29)
    - Cohan, McGehee, Yuriko; Eilber (postcard) (Box-folder 241/30)
    - Gray (Box-folder 241/31)
    - Gray, Kimura (Box-folder 241/32)
    - Hawkins, MG (Box-folder 241/33)
    - Hawkins, MG, O’Donnell, Yuriko; MG, O’Donnell, Yuriko (Box-folder 241/34)
    - Hawkins, Yuriko (Box-folder 241/35)
    - Homsey, Wengerd (Box-folder 241/36)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 241/37)
    - Kimura, and other (Box-folder 241/38)
    - McGehee (Box-folder 241/39)
    - MG (Box-folder 241/40)
    - MG, O’Donnell; MG, O’Donnell, Yuriko (Box-folder 241/41)
    - Monte (Box-folder 241/42)
    - Monte, Parkes (Box-folder 241/43)
    - Ruddy (Box-folder 241/44)
    - Turney (Box-folder 241/45)
    - Washington, Wengerd (Box-folder 241/46)
    - White, Wilber (Box-folder 241/47)
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 241/48)
    - Set (Box-folder 241/49)
  - Circe
    - Asakawa (Box-folder 242/1)
    - Gain, Hinkson, [McDonald], Powell (Box-folder 242/2)
    - Gain, Hinkson, Powell (Box-folder 242/3, 259/2)
    - Gain, Hinkson, Powell, [Randazzo] (Box-folder 242/3, 259/4)
    - Gain, Hinkson, Powell (incl. negatives) (Box-folder 259/3)
    - Gain, Hinkson, others (Box-folder 242/4, 259/5)
    - Gain, Ross, Thompson (Box-folder 242/5)
    - Garay (Box-folder 242/6)
    - Garay, Morin, White (Box-folder 242/7)
    - Hinkson (Box-folder 242/8)
    - Hinkson, [McDonald], [Randazzo], [Ross], Thompson, other (Box-folder 242/9)
    - Hinkson, [McDonald], [Randazzo], Thompson, others (Box-folder 242/10)
    - Hinkson, Powell, Randazzo (Box-folder 242/11)
    - Hinkson, Powell, Randazzo, Ross, Thompson (Box-folder 242/12, 259/6)
    - Hinkson, Powell, Ross (Box-folder 242/13)
    - Hinkson, Ross, Thompson, other (Box-folder 259/7)
    - Hinkson, Thompson, others (Box-folder 242/14)
    - Powell (Box-folder 242/15)
    - Rooks (Box-folder 242/16)
    - Ross, Thompson (Box-folder 242/17)
    - Ross, Thompson, others (Box-folder 242/18)
    - Thompson (Box-folder 242/19)
    - Contact sheets (Box-folder 242/20)
    - Group (Box-folder 242/21)
    - Set (Box-folder 242/22, 259/8)
  - Clytemnestra
    - Asakawa (Box-folder 243/1)
    - Asakawa, Chase, Homsey (Box-folder 243/2)
    - Asakawa, Chase, others (Box-folder 243/3)
    - Asakawa, Parkes (Box-folder 243/4)
    - Asakawa, Powell (Box-folder 243/5)
    - Asakawa, other (Box-folder 243/6)
    - Capucilli, Foreman, Littleford (Box-folder 243/7)
    - Cohan (Box-folder 243/8)
    - Cohan, Graff (Box-folder 243/9)
    - Cohan, McGehee, MG (Box-folder 243/10)
    - Foreman, Lyman, Sherman (Box-folder 243/11)
    - Foreman, others (Box-folder 243/12)
    - Gain (Box-folder 243/13)
    - Gain, MG, Ross (Box-folder 259/9)
    - Graff (Box-folder 243/14)
    - Graff, McGehee, MG (Box-folder 243/15)
    - Graff, McGehee, MG, Ross, Wagoner, other (Box-folder 243/16)
    - Graff, MG, Ross, other (Box-folder 243/17)
    - Graff, McGehee, MG (Box-folder 243/18)
    - Hodes (Linda) (Box-folder 243/19)
    - Kimura (Box-folder 243/20, 259/10)
    - Kuch (Box-folder 243/21)
    - Kuch, Ross, Wagoner, Yuriko (Box-folder 243/22)
    - Kuch, Wagoner, Yuriko, other (Box-folder 243/23)
    - Kuch, other (Box-folder 243/24)
    - Littleford, Lyman, Rooks (Box-folder 243/25)
    - Lyman, Rioult (Box-folder 243/26)
    - McDonald (Box-folder 243/27)
    - McDonald, McGehee, MG, Ross (Box-folder 243/28)